Guide to the Fairchild Semiconductor Corporation: files of Steve Allen, photographer M1038
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- LIC module slides for Norman Doyle presentations (uA732, 758, 706, 753, 758, 3075 1/24/73 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Some Taiwan slides for Chuck Smith 10/73 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Slides shot at MOD for Ray Gouldsberry 9/18/73 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- LIC wafer defect photos for Dick Forrest (Cecilia Thatcher) 10/73 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Module photos and film positives for Ron Ulibarri, shiprock 5/73 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- FNA 45 5/73 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Tom Simmons slides showing LED and auto modules 9/73 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- FNA 37 copy photo for Bill Callahan 8/73 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Multi-chip substrate for Bob Marshall 3/73 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Chassis layout slides Copy's 3/73 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- LIC facility photos for H. Sello, USSR proposal with Hugh Mays 1/10/73 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Auto products slides for Bud Oliver 2/73 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Slides of IMS equipment for Paul Danner 6/73 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- New analog products slides for Will Steffe 10/73 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- 73EIC conf. photos for Frank Perrino 9/73 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Materials production slides for Bob Walker presentation to Healdsbug town council 3/73 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Photos for Dist. Mktg. news letter- Susan Simmons 1973 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Progress 11/73 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Progress 12/73 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Photos for Scientific American article on advanced IC's 5/73 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Jakarta flip chart pix 10/73 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- New film bonding method for Jim Smith, Jerry McNeal and Paul Turner 10/73 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Foreign businessmen with Dr. Hogan and others in boardroom photos for Scalise 12/12/73 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Career Caravan at Nairobi Village, E. Palo Alto for Bill Callahan 2/19/73 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Junior Achievement award Gene White 2/73 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Career Caravan photos for Bill Callahan 1/73 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Singapore plant shots for Don Brettner 3/74 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Wappinger's Falls MOS plant aerial view (poor) 5/74 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Slide of Jakarta plant from print supplied by Veronica Kane 9/75 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- New narrow 24 pin DIP pkg in comparison with old wide package for Rick McCarthy 12/74 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- 7075 open lead frame for Louis Kawamoto 12/74 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- 78MG- 79MG packages for the agency and press releases 12/74 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Packaging comparison & copy negs for Jim Eick and Frank Perrino 3/74 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Internegs from discrete package renderings 3/74 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Progress 9/74 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Progress 8/74 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Progress 7/74 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Progress 6/74 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Progress, May 1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Progress 4/74 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Management development brochure photos for Veronica [Kan] 1/74 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Progress 1/74 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Sherman Fairchild Scholarship Award winners for 1974 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Pile of Chips 10/74 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Progress 11/74 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Four SEM copies for Bob Seeds 1/24/74 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- 1974 Sales conference photos (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Old manual and new automatic bonders for Geo. Wells slide presentation to analysts [10/78?] (Box 20, Folder 19)
- uA753 open lead frame for Larry Brown 12/74 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- 7075 open packages for Louis Kawamoto 11/74 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Voltage regulator package slides for Bill Matlack 9/74 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- TBF401, TGH345, TGH366 open packages for Rubin Silva, Dennis Shelton 5/74 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- CCd packages 4/74 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- DO-7 package drawing slides 4/74 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- MS 101 open package photo for Vic Patel 3/74 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- TGF-0373 open package for Ron Kovacs 3/74 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- 4K9 TTL multi-chip memory for Gary Adams, company private 4/74 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Interneg of Voltage reg. and photomicrograph background 8/74 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- 7387 open pkg for Jim Eick 3/74 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Film lead frames for Ralph Olberg 7/74 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- 0320 on header for Haluck Aytak 6/74 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Copy of agency photo Composite of CCd package for Jim Courtice and Nancy Bohnet 6/74 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- 16 and 22 lead DIP comparison photo for Gene Miles article- Allen Snyder, Adv. 6/74 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Watch component slides for Don Pezzolo 12/74 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- DIC CAD mask design area for Rick Rossell 1/74 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Materials area shots for Cliff Roe 2/74 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Olivetti printing calculator slides Phil Thomas 1/74 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Jakarta pix from poor color prints for Don Brettner 3/74 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Transistor wafer scribing pix for Alan MacPherson for use by Arnold & Porter in D.C. 11/74 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Copy negs from Chicago Show booth photos 7/74 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- DOD slide talk, MOS control line, etc. for Ron Byrne 11/74 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- CMOS manufacturing area in bldg. #1 for Paul Reagan 1/74 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Systems Technology Div. plant in San Jose 10/74 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Fairchild F-100 pocket calculator mockup photos 5/74 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- TV Freq. Synthesizer display board, Eric Breeze 10/74 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- New radio/audio modules 5/74 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- More auto slides from Bob Hood's area for Jack Leone 5/74 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Copy of rendering of new warehouse between Bldg 13and Bldg 20 parking lot 4/74 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- 9374 press release photo 12/74 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Ultrasonic bump bonder in Rex Rice's area for Wright-Patterson Display (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Gate Array Div., Milpitas misc. from Francine Plaza 1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- LIC Hi Rel area for Larry Wittenbaugh promo photos 1/27/83 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- FSC safety & environmental conf. attendees for Mas Koketsu 9/87 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Horizons also various PR photos for Francine 3,4/87 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Fairchild/WestonCCD, Hamilton-Avnet agreement; for Patti Lippe, Jim Johnson 1/86 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Dudy Dyck recieving author's check at Fairch/Weston CCD 1/86 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Susan Mason 12/3/86 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Cebu, Phillipines 1983 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Slides of foreign plants for sales conference 2/78 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Unidentified slides (Box 22, Folder 10)
- uLogic Group hdqts 450 National Ave., Mtn View 7/84 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Shirley Adamik, international 3/77 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Automotive slide presentations continued....... 5/83 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Internegs for Hybrids sales brochure 4/8 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Linear World, for Pat Reed 6/82 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Burleigh Cook's MIS revue slides including shots in data processing 5/76 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Slides of various LIC people for 110 filmstrips for the vans 11/76 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Margaret: August Benson, emp. of the month. For Donna Pombo 8/7/87 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Bev Allen, Benson emp. of the month (May or June?) for Donna Pombo 5/15/87 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Bill Pappani, Benson emp. of the mo. 10/13/87 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Alan Williams, Benson emp. of the mo. 9/11/87 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Steve Lieb, Benson 10/12/87 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Thick Film shot for corp. recruiting brochure; Rich Johanson 11/7/83 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- SPOR photos for Horizons 7/87 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Electronic Products mag, prod of the year award to Howard Sachs and Staff (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Kulwant Egan recieving authors check from Neal Lambert 7/17/87 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Hamilton/Fairchild BBQ for Joanne Berdeen 8/19/86 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Zevatech equipment being off loaded at Bldg 19 11/83 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Linear Div. Bldg 2 & 1 4/83 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Basford/Allen promo photos 6/83 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Puyllup assembly and test orientation slides for Dennis Leach 11/83 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Military briefcase, LARAM 11/76 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Military Briefcase #34 display for Mike Scott 3/76 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Linear fab and wafer test, slides for Warren Johnson 3/83 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Fairchild gate Arrays/ Priam press release photos 12/4/84 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- MOS reliability brochure C.J Stell, Erika Fincher 6/3/82 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Slides from Don Severson's new hire program 9/82 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Nagasaki, Japan plant for Don Brooks video 5/85 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Schlumberger headquarters New York City '86 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Nagasaki shot showing new fab building, neg from Francine Plaza 9/86 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Eric Breeze's multiple TV images 11/77 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Bldg 20 with beautiful clouds and Charlotte Maurer and Randy Holladay candids 7/77 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Healdsburg plant from a 35 mm color slide 5/77 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Linear & Hybrid Prods. Div. hdqts, 313 Fairchild Dr., Mtn View 7/84 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Surinder Krishna X4476 7/7/83 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Ja MEs Kuo 8/17/83 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- George Lechner, for Linear World 1/10/83 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Earthquacke report photos Brad Bushman, Lee Neal 7/15/87 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- FSC corporate headquarters Cupertino 8/86 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Gunn High School physics with teacher - Art Farmer 10/84 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Exetron building, 3105 Alfred, Santa Clara 4/76 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- More E.T. Fairchild store photots showing sign changes for Corp. Legal 1/77 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Gate Array Div. Milpitas 8/86 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Puyallup (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Puyallup latest building dupe slide from Travis Design, also a 4x5 dupe from my 'chrome 1986 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Puyallup, 2nd stage const. progress photos plus architect's model 2/85 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Mask Shop, 441 Whisman Rd Mountain View, CA 2/87 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Momentum, etc 10/87 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Aug 1987 photos for Francine Plaza (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Peyton Cole 2/87 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Graphics chip designers (Roger Reak) on right, for Cheryl Pastone 12/16/87 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Watch module furnace in Bldg 19 for Carol Perker 6/76 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- VIC Herbert for Linear World article on QA 3/84 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Francine Plaza 6/84 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Analog picnic 10/4/87 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Second source agreement signing, Gate Arrays-VTI, for Mike Hollabaugh 5/84 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- uA212 demo boards, etc. 2/7/86 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- TCE machine for 10/21/82 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Hybrid Products Div. 369 Whisman Road, Mountain View 5/13/82 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Hybrid brochure photos for Bob Wallace 2/78 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- SALES Update, both SPOR and MV 2/87 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- More Surelink trademark photos for Lee Patch, Dave Barnes 4/21/87 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Multiplexer copy photo for Mike Adams 5/4/87 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Discovery '86 at Red Lion Inn, San Jose, 4/22/86 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Update photos Salem 8/86 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- FSC/Hitachi PR photos 6/27/86 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- 1987 Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Hybrid assembly and test, photos for Al Chu - Hong Kong (Box 25, Folder 13)
- New photos and internegs from old photos for Delco Proposal 12/83 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Sales Conference 2/78 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Wescon 1978 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Dist. Mktg. portable trade show display for Tom McGuire 5/78 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- SBC50 board 2/7/86 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- PROGRESS cover 2/78 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- LYN Christenson 2/78 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Dennis Kundsin Strategic planning 11/22/78 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Claudio Bortoluz from a bad 35mm color slide 6/78 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Murray McLachlan 3/29/78 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Lou Pighi, from a copy neg 3/78 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- John Davies 3/78 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Dick Belcher 2/78 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- John Giblin, portrait and passport photos 2/78 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Y.I. Lee 11/21/86 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Mike Hernandez 1/86 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Photo of Opto parts for line card 7/78 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- TTL Databookcover 8/25/78 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Interface databook cover 8/25/78 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Slide internegs from optical coin sorter thing and avionics on F16 fighter artwork '78 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- uA212TK Designer's kit for data sheets, IC Master and Sales Update, 10/1/86 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- FSP100 Evaluation Board 10/14/86 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- John Miller and Dave Miller for Sales Update 8/86 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Miscellaneous photographs and negatives (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Burn-in ovens for Mike Kehir 1/77 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- MOS slides used by McLaren Steinhauer for filmstrips 1977 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Plating shop brochure pix 10/77 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Jim Chastain's mfg. capability slides 5/77 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- GAsP materials area spec photos for Frank Dosatalek 12/76 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- CMOS areas, Bldgs 1 & 2 for John Domingo 10/76 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- Ron Rule's test terminals 1977 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- Misc. mafg scenes, slides (some older stuff) '77 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- TO-3 pkg handler for Don Lapray 6/77 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- HEMRAJ (HEM) HINGARH 11/76 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Harry Sello Sept '76 (Box 25, Folder 48)
- John Wyatt and Tat Blesch 4/76 (Box 25, Folder 49)
- Barbara Prince 8/76 (Box 25, Folder 50)
- Mug shots of Mktg Svs crew for Art Heller's going-away picture album 1/76 (Box 25, Folder 51)
- Slides from b&w aerial view showing Mountain View complex 8/76 (Box 25, Folder 52)
- Progress photos of Bldg 42 for Hal Edelstein Bill Evans 3/76 (Box 25, Folder 53)
- Voltage regulator packages for Russ Apfel 2/76 (Box 25, Folder 54)
- ALIC fab 4/18/84 (Box 25, Folder 55)
- CCD linear and area Imaging packages for Joel Miller 7/22/77 (Box 25, Folder 56)
- Timeband $19.95 watch pix for John Hatch 6/30/77 (Box 25, Folder 57)
- Stacks of Cannone documentation for Bob Bostic 7/16/87 (Box 25, Folder 58)
- Eutectic photos for Wally Fiedler 10/14/87 (Box 25, Folder 59)
- VeriFone credit card verifiers; MODEM applications for Dave Barnes 5/87 (Box 25, Folder 60)
- Miscellaneous negatives and photographs (Box 25, Folder 61)
- Miscellaneous negatives and photographs (Box 25, Folder 62)
- Miscellaneous negatives and photographs (Box 25, Folder 63)
- SH1605 and 1705 for Jerry Markus press releases 4/78 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- SH 3015 sealed device for Jerry Markus press releases 4/78 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Digital bathroom scale boards for Bob Bobrink 9/77 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Autocomp on Board uP computer for cars by Spacekom Slides for Dr. Hogan 7/77 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Polar Bears from PROGRESS 6/77 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Progress 3/77 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Displays for Hamilton-Avnet, and Schwebber booths 3/77 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Copy negs from photos of the Electronika German trade show for Geri Hadley 8/77 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Pix of Sherry listening to tape player for PROGRESS 6/77 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- 3I7302 header for Carol Wood 4/18/83 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Bipolar memory databook cover photo, packages, for Apex Reed (Box 26, Folder 11)
- 21-Solid State Microwaves MS-100 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- TO-18 header photos for Haren Joshi 1/78 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Diode Databook cover for Bill Matlack 8/31/78 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Small Signal data book cover photo 11/27/78 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- LIC fab traming slides for Margaret 5/6/82 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Laser fuse cutter for redundent 64K DRAM; Ramesh Varshne 3/17/82 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Photos for Fairtech brochure, Gene Casstevens (A,N & B) may have some chromes 12/48 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- MOS test area for Harriett brochure 3/76 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- CB synthesizer for Eric Breeze 6/23/76 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Hughs wafer cell photo for Chris Ladas, puyallup 12/4/84 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Gate Array package, and Les, for Schl. annual 1/15/86 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- MODEM Designer's Kit for HORIZONS 5/14/86 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Data Disc (Box 26, Folder 24)
- FLPA- Diode Light Pulser Array (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Linear fab training photos 1/83 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Epoxy packages-general views (Box 26, Folder 27)
- FGE6300 devices for slides and press release photos 6/86 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Mini sales conference photos 4/76 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- uA212AT and V22 block diagrams for Dave Barnes 6/3/87 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- E & E MODEM for Chris Newham 6/8/87 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Copy negs from scope traces Ralph Locher Prelim. data sheet 7/87 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Electric meter photos for Robert Leydier 6/30/87 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- VR wafer, for Derek Kernan 6/87 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- 0360 (7310) pkg photos for Jeff Kwok 2/76 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Dynawatt package photos for Dale Lillard and Finn Wilhemson 1/76 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Random Photographs (Box 26, Folder 37)
- Random Photographs (Box 26, Folder 38)
- POWER CON for Helene 10/7/86 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Discrete hi rel slides for Haren Joshi (Box 26, Folder 40)
- uA212TK Designer's Kit for Jessica 9/22/86 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- Mask shop, Whisman Rd. for Harold Short (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Color Photos for Dist. Mktg. microprocessor booth 3/77 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- Ignition Module Assembly display board photos for Jerry Markus 4/77 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- Ignition module assembly display board photos for Jerry Markus 10/77 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- 79HG press release Jerry Markus 8/77 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- Substrate for Jerry Markus and consumer show 5/77 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- SH 3015 for Jerry Markus 1/78 (Box 26, Folder 48)
- Hybrid brochure update photos for Bill Matlack 7/24/78 (Box 26, Folder 49)
- VR demo kit for R. Smith 1/78 (Box 26, Folder 50)
- Voxson module for cover of 4th quarterly report 1977 11/77 (Box 26, Folder 51)
- SH3011 package for Jerry Markus press release 11/77 (Box 26, Folder 52)
- 78PO5SC and 78HO5ASC sealed VR pkgs for Marcus PR 12/77 (Box 26, Folder 53)
- Automotive & Hybrid pkg display board (improved) (Box 26, Folder 54)
- Voxson car radio with our hybrid module superimposed for Jerry Markus 12/16/77 (Box 26, Folder 55)
- Hybrid packaging display board and emulator for Jerry Marcus and area Manager 2/28/77 (Box 26, Folder 56)
- Copy neg from old "thanks Seymour" dist. mktg. group shot about 1974 (Box 26, Folder 57)
- AIM accelerator machine photos for Mike Barranti 6/27/78 (Box 26, Folder 58)
- Dr. John McCue 10/13/86 (Box 26, Folder 59)
- Ralph Locher's negs 9/11/87 (Box 26, Folder 60)
- Momentum 3,4,5,/87 (Box 26, Folder 61)
- July photos for Francine Plaza 7/87 (Box 26, Folder 62)
- Momentum 2/87 (Box 26, Folder 63)
- Basic Data Handbook (Box 26)
- Horizons 4/86 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- 1987 Facilities & MFG Scenes (Empty folder) (Box 27, Folder 2)
- New Channel F games for John Hatch's press kits 12/77 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- New photos for recruiting brochure update 4/86 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Hybrid facilities, capabilities, and products for automotive slides presentations 5/83 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- 38E70 pkg for Joe Fowler 5/20/82 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Jim Holt's slide pitch 1/86 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- IC amp. packages for press releases 4/76 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- James Hodges, Corp. QA 1/28/86 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Jean Ribound, deceased, pres. of Schlumberger 1/86 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- CMOS Gate Array pkgs for Mag cover; Dave Werry 9/15/83 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Linear fab and assembly WFO Orientation program 3/38 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Misc. slides back from Francine 6/86 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Random Photographs (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Linear fab slides 1984? (Box 27, Folder 15)
- LIC failure analysis lab for LINEAR WORLD 3/84 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Power One power supply for Frank Flens 1/23/84 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- MODEM boards for Theo Janson 6/84 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- LIC buildings and fabs for Jerry Pettigrew's line maint. recruiting show 6/84 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- TO-66 packages for Ron Ricci 1/76 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- LIC package layout for Russ Floyd 3/76 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Additional slides for Bipin Shah's Desc Presentation 1/84 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- FCCD shots with Pat O'connel of Bernanrd Hodes for college recruiting brochure update 12/83 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- TV games color photo for John Hatch 7/76 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Timeband clock and watchs for Bill Matlack 9/76 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Technology auto clock kit for Opto 8/76 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- 9440 device and PC board comparison slides for Peter Verhofstadt 11/76 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- F100K ECL Sysytems Test Demo Unit for Jim Hively and Mike Scott 3/16/76 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous slides 1982 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Gate Array design facility slides for Robert Nalesnik 2/82 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Stopwatch, Cronograph, and large digit watches 4/78 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- F-8 Formulator and boards with manuals for Charley Dice 7/78 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- So. SJ manf. scenes for John Hatch and the SJ Mercury 5/2/78 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- Winchester disk drive for Jerry Frazee 2/84 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- Jim Holt 11/16/84 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- Larry Amon 10/84 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- John Migliore, NAS VP Mktg. 10/84 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Tom Palamenghi 8/28/84 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- Dave Miller 11/9/84 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- Tom Roberts 11/81 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- 1987 Hardware (Empty) (Box 27, Folder 41)
- Focus XVI for Electronica trade show 9/78 (Box 27, Folder 42)
- Plastic pkgs on uA759 chip photo background, for Bill C. 12/76 (Box 27, Folder 43)
- Massed transistor packages for Descrete 110 film strips, Ed Valentine, McLaren Steinhauee 12/76 (Box 27, Folder 44)
- Slides for Leo Lehner's packaging pitch 6/76 (Box 27, Folder 45)
- New package for Bill Matlack, Dist. Mktg. 12/76 (Box 27, Folder 46)
- 93452 & 53 PROM package photos for Bill Matlack 12/76 (Box 27, Folder 47)
- More TO-92 type lead frames for Maxine, transistor failure analysis 9/76 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- Open and sealed PROM pkgs for Bill Matlack and Dick Lamy 7/76 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- 741 JAN package photos for Mary Valmoja 3/76 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- Open pkg color photos for ED mag cover- 3851, CCD460, and 3843 (Mostek) 5/76 (Box 27, Folder 51)
- VL05 EI package photo for Cecilia Thatcher 7/76 (Box 27, Folder 52)
- Extra copy prints of watch line 5/76 (Box 27, Folder 53)
- Extra slides from Bob Dwyer MOS presentation (Microprocessor) 3/76 (Box 27, Folder 54)
- Master SET I.C. Brochure (Box 27, Folder 55)
- TWN lead frames for Walt Heinzer and Bill Carrico 8/12/76 (Box 27, Folder 56)
- TO-92 frame comparison (club head vs. TON) for John Leith 1/76 (Box 27, Folder 57)
- 78HG open package for Bill Sliver, Rodney Smith 12/76 (Box 27, Folder 58)
- TV games PC board for Carol Parker 9/76 (Box 27, Folder 59)
- Don Brooks for Stan at EE Times 10/29/86 (Box 27, Folder 60)
- Renee Bader, Cupertino Sales 3/5/87 (Box 27, Folder 61)
- F6856 pkg for press & release Joe Fowler, uP Div. 7/82 (Box 27, Folder 62)
- uA77000 pkg on 7759 chip for Denny Henderson 8/82 (Box 27, Folder 63)
- Miscellaneous negatives and photographs (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Whole VR wafer for Reg Simspon 9/28/83 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- 7360 wafer for Reg Simpson 10/04/83 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Chemical dispenser fire photos for Lee Neal 6/24/76 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Slides showing various pkg types for Martha Sessums' trip to Jakarta or somewhere 6/78 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- 3850 and 3853 unsealed pkgs for Roger Haynie 9/78 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- FS-1 Multi-User System 7/1/82 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Pkg groupings from Puyallup for Gary Hines 3/86 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Bubble pack for power packages 6/78 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- F16K sealed package 6/19/78 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- MOS package types for Finn Wilhemsen 6/27/78 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- uA78S40 for Tony C. pkg 4/78 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- 9411 DIP package 5/78 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- uA9708 pkg for Tony C 4/78 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- uA9706 pkg for Tony C. 4/78 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- THD 320 4/78 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Cover photo for voltage regulator handbook 3/78 (Box 28, Folder 17)